Maulik Patel

WFB DESIGNER

mpatel0890@gmail.com

@maulik-patel

Limited working proficiency

PROFILE

I am Web Designer with 5+ years of experience. I always strive to write clean, elegant and modular code using the latest web standards such as SASS, LESS. My goal is to create professional quality websites with responsive in a time bound manner. Also, I'm a good team player & love to communicate with my colleagues

SKILLS

HTML5 CSS3

Bootstrap

jQuery

Javascript

SCSS/LESS

Angular Js

DESIGN TOOLS

Adobe Photoshop Adobe Illustrator Adobe XD **Figma** Zeplin

LANGUAGES

English Hindi Gujrati

WORK EXPERIENCE

EXECUTIVE WEB DESIGNER

DRC Systems

May 2021 - Present

- · Assisted engineering team to define requirements from creative team on their HTML pages needs.
- Translated necessary requirements into HTML code.
- Ensured that personal technical skills are kept up to date for effective development.
- Resolved all issues professionally and in a timely manner.

WEB DESIGNER

Bexcode Services

Oct 2020 - May-2021

- Coordinated with back end developers and business for website requirements.
- Partnered with internal and external suppliers to create and maintain content.
- Work on Convert PSD to HTML with responsive design

WEB DESIGNER

TridhyaTech

Mar 2019 - Aug 2020

- Maintained and ensured to enhance the company's multi-branded websites.
- Gathered all project requirements with 95% fidelity to client needs.
- Work on Convert PSD to HTML with responsive design

WEB DESIGNER

ManekTech

Sept 2016 - Jan 2019

- Starting career with Application Design and taken more grip on webdesign.
- Learning coding standard with W3C validator and try to make standard code.
- Converted 15+ PSD design to HTML with responsive design.

EDUCATION HISTORY

Bachelors of Computer Applications

HNGU University

Mar 2009 - Jun 2012